

ANDY CHEN

North Jakarta, Indonesian • andychen9979@gmail.com • (+62) 812-6700-6823 andychen00.github.io • linkedin.com/in/andy-chen-78504620b

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Andy Chen is a developer with 3 year of experience. He serves as a junior developer in his company now. Beside that, he also have a lot of knowledge in software development such us programming skill, system development, UI/UX design and many else. he also already done several of project about web and mobile application.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Evotech Distribusi Co. (IT solution prodiver)

Mobile and Web Developer Intern

Puri Kembangan, West Jakarta Feb 2022 – Feb 2023

- Built, develop and maintain web/mobile application for warehouse project based using Outsystems
- Perform bug fixing or debugging for developed application that can help to optimize and maintain the app well
- Collaborating with UI/UX designer to ensure the design were efficient and tecnically sound
- Assist in gathering user requirement, design UI application and user acceptance testing
- Ensuring proper documentation and report of all programs

Ifabula Digital Kreasi Co. (IT solution prodiver)

Junior Developer (Outsystem Developer)

Green Lake City, Tangerang Feb 2023 – Now

- Improve my skill and knowledge of using Outsystems
- Working with a team project and comunation with client to discuss user requirement for project
- Have experience in managing, collaborating and communicating well in a team
- Integrating with REST API in my project
- Working with SSMS databases and performing queries

EDUCATION

Binus University

Bachelor of Computer

Major in Computer Science – Mobile Application and Technology

Kemanggisan, West Jakarta August 2019 - 2023

PROJECTS HANDLE

Gudang2Go (Warehouse Web and Mobile Application)

- Designed, developed, and maintained web/mobile applications for warehouse projects
- Debugged and resolved application issues to ensure smooth functionality
- Worked alongside UI/UX designers to create efficient design and user friendly application
- Participated in gathering user needs, designing user interfaces, and performing user acceptance tests
- Produced comprehensive documentation and detailed reports for all program in application

IRIS Monitoring (Website for monitoring internal working system)

- Built, develop and maintain web application for IRIS Monitoring Project
- Collaborated on team projects while communicating with clients to determine user requirements
- Gained experience in teamwork, including managing, cooperating, and fostering strong communication within teams
- Create report and documentation for all program in the application

BOA/ Back Office Aggregator (Website for manage bank transaction for internal used)

- Improve the BOA project that already exist and develop new feature for the application
- Collaborated on team projects to discuss about the improvement of the application
- Gained experience in teamwork, including managing and cooperating with different team
- Incorporated REST APIs into projects to ensure seamless integration.
- Utilized SSMS databases to perform advanced queries and data management.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Technical: Java, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Outsystems, Relational Database, RESTful API
- Tools: Android Studio, Outsystems, VSCode, SSMS
- Languages: English, Mandarin, Indonesian
- Certifictions & Training: HMS foundation course, OS Developer